http://www.steelerubber.com/privacy

Checkout
0 items ( $0.00 )
View the Full Cart
Fire & Rescue VehiclesHome Additional Seals and Rubber Parts Cabin and Crew Door Seals Compartment Door Seals Window and Glass SealsAdhesives & Tools Restoration PartsManualsBumpers, Screw AttachedBumpers, Stem Bumpers Chassis Body Mount Kits Body Mount Pad Fittings Body Parts, Other Clutch, Brake, Transmission Brake & Clutch Pedals Clutch and Brake, Misc Others Drive Shaft Support Transmission Mounts Convertible Convertible Front Bow Weatherstrip Convertible Hinge Pillars Convertible Parts, Other Convertible Roof Rail Weatherstrip Kits Door Door Bumper Stops Door Handle & Lock Door Parts, Other Door Weatherstrip Door Weatherstrip by the foot Door Weatherstrip, Auxiliary Electrical Electrical Parts, Other Electrical, Backup and License light Electrical, Headlight Electrical, NonLighting Electrical, Parking, Fogs and Fender Lights Electrical, Tail light Firewall Grommets Engine Engine Mounts Engine, Other Harmonic Balancers Front & Rear Bumper Parts Front Bumper Parts Rear Bumper Parts Fuel System Accelerator Pedal Exhaust System Fuel Filler Neck Grommets Fuel System Parts, OtherGrommets Hardtop Weatherstrip Hardtop Roof Rail Weatherstrip T-Top/Targa Weatherstrip Hood, Cowl & Fender Body and Fender Fillers Cowl Vent Fittings Fender & Fender Skirt Edging Hood Bumpers & Fittings Hood to Cowl Hood to Radiator Running Board Matting Splash Apron / Dust Shields Stone Shield Interior Interior PartsPlugs, Body Plugs Quarter Window Fixed Quarter Window Rubber Quarter & Side Window Leading Edge Quarter Vent Window Bumpers Sliding Quarter Window Rubber U-jamb Seals Radiator & Grill Grill Heating & Cooling Radiator Rear Window Rear Window Division Bar Rear Window Weatherstrip Rear Window Weatherstrip by the foot Rear Window Weatherstrip, Auxiliary Side Window Run Channel Bumpers Side Window Parts, Other Side Window Run Channel Components Side Window Run Channel Kits Side Window Sash Channel Side Window Seal Kits Window Felt Components Window Felt Weatherstrip (Inners Only) Window Felt Weatherstrip (Outers only) Window Felt Weatherstrip Kits Steering & Suspension Shock Absorber Spring Stabilizer Steering Suspension Trunk & Tailgate Tailgate Parts, Other Tailgate Weatherstrip Trunk Parts, Auxiliary Trunk Parts, Other Trunk Weatherstrip Trunk Weatherstrip by the foot Vent Window Front Door Vent Window Rubber Quarter Vent Window Rubber Rear Door Vent Window Rubber Vent Window Division Post Seals Wheels Spare Wheel Carrier Wheel
Parts Windshield Windshield Division Bar Windshield Gasket Windshield Weatherstrip by the foot Windshield Wiper Transmission Windshield, Auxiliary Windshield, Other Body Kits Glass Kits Body Bumper KitsMarine WeatherstripHome Adhesives & Tools Cabin & Compartment Doors Hatches & Edge Trim Rub Rails & Insert Trim Windows, Glass & Port HolesFeatured PartsGrommets, Plugs & BumpersRVHome Doors Hatches & Insert Trim Slide-Outs Universal Parts, Adhesives & Tools WindowsAdhesives & ToolsAir Conditioning - Heat Pump GasketsGrommets, Plugs, & BumpersSteele RubberHome Accessories Adhesives & Tools Marine Weatherstrip Racing Parts RV Parts Steele Logo Apparel Street Rod Parts Universal Parts
Search for Parts
Select Year
2011
2012
2013
2014
2015
2016
G Champion
G.T.O.
G10
G10 Beauville
G10 Custom Sportvan
G10 Deluxe Sportvan
G10 Panel
G10 Panel Van
G10 Sportvan
G15
2 door Pickup Coupe
2 door Pickup (Highside)
2 door Pickup (Lowside)
2 door Pickup Stake
2 door Plainback Sedan
2 door Platform
2 door Platform 12 Foot Bed
2 door Platform 7.5 Foot Bed
2 door Platform 7 Foot Bed
2 door Platform 9.5 foot
2 door Platform 9.5 Foot Bed
5 door Sport Utility
loading...
Need Assistance?
We are here to help.
Call 800-447-0849
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your Personal Information
You may be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information when you visit The Steele Rubber Products website in order for us to provide you with the products or services that you have requested. You may be asked for your phone number, shipping and billing addresses, your email address, and your credit card number or other payment-related information. We utilize your phone number as a unique identifier to help us maintain your transaction history. Additionally, our Web Servers may track various technical details about your visit, such as your computer's IP address and which pages you visited. That information does not typically contain any personally identifiable information about you.
The information we collect is used to provide the products and services that you have requested or in which we think that you might have an interest. It is also used to improve the content of our website, to notify you of problems with your requests, or to update you about changes to our website.
Any personal information you have on record with Steele Rubber Products is held in strict confidence. You may request changes or revisions to this information by contacting us directly. Due to various legal and recordkeeping requirements, however, we may be required to maintain records about your purchases or other activities. You will always be permitted to opt-out of any marketing uses of your personal information. To request changes or revisions, please contact us:
Steele Rubber Products
6180 E. NC 150 HWY
Denver, NC 28037
704-483-9343
email us
Sharing Information
We occasionally need to share information with third parties in order to operate this website and in order to provide you with the products and services you have requested. We may transmit your personal information to service providers who assist us in processing orders, shipping products, processing payment information, sending catalogs and sending emails. We have agreements with these service providers that they will protect your privacy in accordance with our standard Privacy Statement. Some of those organizations may have their own privacy statements which may give you additional protections.
Legal Disclosures
If required by law, we may provide any and all information we have about you to law enforcement or other government agencies, pursuant to a subpoena, warrant, or other order by a court of competent jurisdiction. In all cases, we will require written documentation of the request, proof of the identity of the law enforcement official making the request, and we will take steps to authenticate the validity of the request. Any law enforcement or government agency request submitted with less than a court-issued order will be evaluated on a case-by-case basis according to the need and urgency as well as the particular law enforcement agency making the request.
Communications
If you provide us with your email address, you may receive messages about your order status, website updates, product information or marketing promotions. You may modify your email preferences by calling 704-483-9343 or email us.
If you provide us with your postal address, you may receive periodic catalogs from us or other notices containing information about products, services and events. If you do not wish to receive postal mailings from Steele Rubber Products, please let us know by calling, sending an email, or writing to us. Please provide us with your exact name and postal address
SECURITY
Steele Rubber Products values your business and is committed to doing everything possible to make our online ordering process secure. As always, our 100% satisfaction guarantee applies to any and all purchases from Steele Rubber Products.
Secure Ordering Process
Any credit card information you enter on our site is strongly encrypted by industry-standard protocol, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). The Steele Rubber Products website uses SSL to communicate with secure browsers like Firefox, Netscape, and Internet Explorer. These browsers encrypt your credit card and personal information in a way that makes it extremely difficult for anyone to intercept and misuse while being transmitted between your computer and our server.
Once you have completed your order online, our security procedures do not end. We take appropriate precautions to protect the security and privacy of the information stored on our computer networks. Many of the systems which store your personal information are not connected to the Internet, reducing the likelihood of security breaches. Our systems are also housed in secure facilities, and access to your data by our employees is limited to a "need to know" basis, controlled by password protected systems, and monitored for abuse.
If you are still unsure of giving your credit card over the Internet, please feel free to phone, fax, or mail your order to us. For telephone ordering or assistance, please call 800-447-0849. Our fax number for orders is 800-483-6650. Or send your order to:
Steele Rubber Products
Attn: Order Processing
6180 E. NC 150 HWY
Denver, NC 28037
Children
In accordance with federal law, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13 without the verifiable permission of a parent or guardian. If you are under age 13, you are welcome to browse our website. However you are not permitted to use any of the features of our site that require the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we determine that we have erroneously collected a child's information, we will immediately undertake to delete that data from our records.
